Revenge can be a bitch.
Even Lambs Have Teeth is a thriller, horror film directed by Terry Miles.
Two young women terrorized by a group of small town
psychos seek revenge on their tormentors.
Sloane, played by Kirsten Zien.
Katie, played by Tiera Skovbye.
Travis, played by Darren Mann.
Jason, played by Michael Karl Richards.
Vince, played by Manny Jacinto.
Sheriff Andrews, played by Craig March.
Even Lambs Have Teeth is a 2015 Canadian-French rape and revenge film written and
directed by Terry Miles and starring Kirsten Prout and Tiera Skovbye.
The film tells the story of two young women who take revenge on the
sex trafficking ring that kidnapped and abused them.
The tone is dark and intense.